

- Address Ho Shi Min 57a Skopje - Macedonia
- Phone number +389 70 700 572
- E-mail ktdportfolio@gmail.com
- www.ktd-design.com
- www.visiva.io
- Nationality Macedonian
- Date of birth 05.08.1984
- Sex Male
- Native language macedonian
- Other languages english, partial german

Social and organizational skills

Adaptability

Organization

Teamwork

Individual work

Communicability

Flexibility

Creativity

Initiative

Technical skills

Web Design

Logo Design

Corporate Identity & Branding

Packaging

Print Design

Typography

Infographic

Banner Design

UI/UX

Tools















Interests

- Hiking
- Baksetball
- House music

KRISTIJAN TRAJCHEV

Graphic and UI UX designer



About Me

I am Kristijan a visual Brand designer with almost 10 years of experience in Graphic design and more than 4 years in UI/UX. I am hard working, well organized, responsible and reliable person who is eager to learn new things. I can contribute to the company with my rich experience as a Graphic and UI/UX designer, my communication skills, flexibility, ability to learn and work as a member of a team or individually. I may not have a formal art deegree but I do feel like I have a well of creativity inside, and tons of ideas on my mind, ready to be shaped into a project.

Education

Education	
Skillshare, Lynda.com, Udemy Online courses for Graphic design.	2010 - 2011
European University - Faculty of Economics - Bank Menagement Title - Graduate Economist	2004 - 2010
High School "Orce Nikolov" Skopje	2000 - 2004
Work Experience	
A88Lab. Creative SaaS Agency	2021 - 2022
Visiva - Digital Marketing Agency	2020 - 2021
Clikdaq	2018 - 2020
Designcrowd, Upwork, private clients Type of work - Graphic designer - Freelance, contracts, remote jobs. Main activities - Logo design, Branding, Packaging, UI/UX, Print design, Web banners, Social Media, Infographics	2012
Viva Miki Skopje · · · · · · · · · · · · · · · · · · ·	2009 - 2012

Awards

1st place - Logo design and B-cards

Main activities - Managing Transport Company.

assisting and conducting marketing campaigns.

Type of work - Promoter, Coordinator, Marketing Assistant

Atlas computer services - https://jobs.designcrowd.com/job.aspx?id=999316

Main activities - Promotion of differrent products, coordinating promoter teams,

1st place - T-shirt design

Type of work - Manager

Mountain resort - https://jobs.designcrowd.com/job.aspx?id=2235122

1st place - Logo design

TZ - service - https://jobs.designcrowd.com/job.aspx?id=1151994

1st place - Logo design

Blume and Darling - https://jobs.designcrowd.com/job.aspx?id=1591878

1st place - Logo design

IMI - Iron Mountain Insurance - https://jobs.designcrowd.com/job.aspx?id=817422

Adobe portfolio review

by Adobe Creative Directors - https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=dK-XWGYEI-c&t=134s

Portfolio

www.ktd-design.com www.behance.net/ktddesign www.dribbble.com/kristijan_ktd







